Kostadis Roussos: He goes… As you spoke.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're… I call first. Okay, so are you You call first.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Brother Palmer… What does the other caller do?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. You call first, are you gonna have one?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, then and there, or do you want to, like, perhaps
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so there are… he shows you the three, the three of the fruits that are drugged, and says, just a bite!
Nicholas Roussos: No, not no, not right now.
Kostadis Roussos: So you now have also take three drugged fruits.
Nicholas Roussos: Drugs. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's also the desk to check out, I presume.
Kostadis Roussos: It's gonna look at the desk.
Thomas Kolivakis: The desk, I will look at the desk.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. You find a spell scroll of resist poison.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just put those here.
Kostadis Roussos: Goodbye.
Kostadis Roussos: Find… I should… I need to go put these in here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you find a spell scroll of Resist Poison, a spell scroll of True Seeing, and a spell scroll of Resist Energy Fire. I'll put those in
Kostadis Roussos: Party, I need to put all of these in this party thing, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Let me take care of that later. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You all? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, there's…
Thomas Kolivakis: Well, it's Okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: These are resistance spells.
Kostadis Roussos: The spell scroll of true seeing is a spell scroll that allows you to see anything, traps, etc, the true nature of creatures.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh.
Thomas Kolivakis: Can anyone learn it?
Kostadis Roussos: It's not, you can't learn it, it's a scroll, so you.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: So it's not a, it's not a wizard spell. It's a, it's a scroll. Anyone can cast it, but you can't, you have to be, you can't, you're not a wizard, so you can't learn it. Does that make sense?
Thomas Kolivakis: Yep.
Nicholas Roussos: You are not with.
Kostadis Roussos: All righty.
Thomas Kolivakis: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Oops.
Kostadis Roussos: You're not a wizard, Harry. Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And so there's a door to the south
Kostadis Roussos: Bill Thornton, what's his name?
Kostadis Roussos: Brother Irluj says, it's my bedroom! Do you… must you really plunder my bedroom?
Nicholas Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Calmer, looks at him and says, Brother Ilrich, I am the head of the… your clout, your temple was defeated by the earth elemental. Would you have shown me any more dignity? No, Brother Alber, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Outfits. Palmer looks at him. No, Lord Master Palmer. That's her.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: It's just time you learned that the oblivion edge does not… What?
Nicholas Roussos: Nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. All right. Who goes into the chamber? Zephyr Sequoia?
Nicholas Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys are… you guys are the rogues. Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the south door opens into another green covered room, 10 feet wide and 30 feet long. It holds the… no, I didn't…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on, let me just make sure I'm reading the right description. I'm trying to keep track of all the resources.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, the south door opens into a 10 foot wide, 30 foot long room. It contains a pair of beds separated by a folding screen. By each bed is a small stand, a bronze brazier, and a low stool and a locked chest.
Kostadis Roussos: So, who wants to go check out the chest?
Thomas Kolivakis: More loot.
Thomas Kolivakis: Calmer, let's.
george: Yeah, they're common.
Kostadis Roussos: Homer goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Scott Comer says, I am not the rogue. You are the rogue.
george: You're the leader.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Thomas Kolivakis: Okay, I will do it. He has like the techniques.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, yeah. Yeah, let me go do a flight of hand check on it.
Nicholas Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you,
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty, okay, so, okay, so, okay, the first chest holds clothing.
Kostadis Roussos: Each chest holds clothing, four texts on the elemental evil of water, so, there's, Ritual Book
Kostadis Roussos: Kalmer says, I will be taking these. Brother, you reach!
Kostadis Roussos: Brother Ilitch starts whining about, you know, how he deserves these, and these are really religious materials, and blah blah blah, and then he again reminds him that he's in charge, right?
Kostadis Roussos: So, the techs are worth 250 gold pieces each.
Nicholas Roussos: Mmhm.
Thomas Kolivakis: We're starting with text.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you taking the text or are you leaving the text?
Thomas Kolivakis: Are these texts important to you?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Thomas Kolivakis: Okay, we'll leave.
Kostadis Roussos: Brother.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so 3 texts times 200.
Kostadis Roussos: So, remember to… so you guys, you should have added, what is it?
Kostadis Roussos: 500 gold pieces, plus 465… 63, 563 gold pieces for the treasure you found so far, yeah?
george: That's including the 400 at the beginning.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, that's it, that's total so far.
Nicholas Roussos: I'm gonna wait for the total before I add stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay.
Nicholas Roussos: Dude, we're getting rich, we're gonna need to go buy some stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, you guys have — this is the .
Thomas Kolivakis: Right.
Nicholas Roussos: What?
Thomas Kolivakis: Audio lagged up.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: He became the big bosses, so the victors go the spoils.
Thomas Kolivakis: Another big buff.
Kostadis Roussos: You're the bosses now, man. Like, that's what happens.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: And… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: You find a ceremonial bronze mace.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, let me just put this here.
Kostadis Roussos: And a gold ring with a pearl.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: and two potions of water breathing.
Thomas Kolivakis: In the same room?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: In the chests.
Kostadis Roussos: That, Sequoia opened.
Thomas Kolivakis: You take the potion of water breathing and you fight the elemental water thingy.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not water. It's not water.
Nicholas Roussos: Out of water.
Nicholas Roussos: Does water breathing not just give you air.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you say, N.
Nicholas Roussos: I was hoping the water breathing just gave.
Nicholas Roussos: You air.
Kostadis Roussos: No, the thing is not water, it's a…
Kostadis Roussos: water elemental, does that… it's a kind of an elemental intelligence. Does that make sense?
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, the water itself is?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, the water itself is living.
Nicholas Roussos: Well, that's scary.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so yes. In fact, when you go through the books, you realize
Kostadis Roussos: You start to wonder how much Brother Ilrich knew about this creature.
Kostadis Roussos: And whether he's somebody you should be trusting going forward. Probably not.
Thomas Kolivakis: Well, maybe we can't trust him, but we need him right now.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: We want to make it known that you know his game and that he's on a very tight leash.
Nicholas Roussos: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: Maybe threaten his life a little bit more.
Nicholas Roussos: Yep.
Thomas Kolivakis: So, you know, you're not the big boss anymore, so…
Thomas Kolivakis: No more surprises in these rooms, okay?
Kostadis Roussos: Brother, yes, yes, of course, of course, of course, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Thomas Kolivakis: Next surprise will be meant for you, okay?
Kostadis Roussos: Role intimidation.
Nicholas Roussos: Who has a good intimidation? I have, like, min.
george: Optimization.
george: Excellent.
Thomas Kolivakis: Can someone help me?
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, I got.
Kostadis Roussos: Calmer helps you.
Thomas Kolivakis: I rolled badly both times.
Nicholas Roussos: Damn.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you roll?
Thomas Kolivakis: 9.
Nicholas Roussos: Embarrassing!
Thomas Kolivakis: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Brother Ilitch, acknowledges you.
Thomas Kolivakis: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, and with that, boys and girls, do you want to head back to your, to your lair and rest, because you're down lots of hit points? All right, and now, since you defeated and plundered the Water Temple…
Kostadis Roussos: You are level 9.
Thomas Kolivakis: Well known.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh…
Kostadis Roussos: What are you? You're level 8 right now.
Thomas Kolivakis: I…
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, we're lovely right now.
Thomas Kolivakis: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: So you should be level 9.
Thomas Kolivakis: Let's see what we gain at 11 o'.
Nicholas Roussos: So how much gold did we gain in total?
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see, ahhh…
Kostadis Roussos: So, new games… hold on, I forgot to… I didn't cut and paste the other.
Nicholas Roussos: Magical ambush. If you have the invisible condition when you cast a spell on that creature.
Thomas Kolivakis: Master of Mimicry.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Thomas Kolivakis: There's speed.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so that's…
Thomas Kolivakis: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: 2,400… Okay.
Nicholas Roussos: This each, or…
Kostadis Roussos: Do the cut.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, hold on, hold on, that was how much you found, let me find… let me do the math, give
Kostadis Roussos: 2, 3… And it's 250… Plus 87… What do you want?
Kostadis Roussos: 828.
Kostadis Roussos: And don't forget, you have to subtract 10% for, I'm sorry, wait, hold on.
Nicholas Roussos: There's, oh yeah, there's a TA.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: 745.
Nicholas Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't forget, Dren expects to get paid.
Kostadis Roussos: So I just took the tax offer, right?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, and so now, we have enough time for you guys to raise a level.
Nicholas Roussos: I just did that.
Kostadis Roussos: You did it.
Thomas Kolivakis: Yeah, so I only got one thing.
Nicholas Roussos: No, if I'm invisible, I can give stuff disadvantage, and I assume if something has disadvantage, I get a…
Nicholas Roussos: Mikadak, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. If you're hidden.
Thomas Kolivakis: It says… No, no, no.
Nicholas Roussos: It's very weird. If I'm invisible and I cast a spell, it gets disadvantage.
george: I can walk on water.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you can walk on water now? How convenient.
Nicholas Roussos: You've joined it!
Thomas Kolivakis: Definitely.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Nick, don't.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, no.
Kostadis Roussos: You… you don't for… don't forget.
Nicholas Roussos: So that'.
Kostadis Roussos: spelled.
Kostadis Roussos: Also, because I got really annoyed.
Nicholas Roussos: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: I made it easy. If you want, I made it very easy to look at RPG bots.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, no, I don't need any.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't, you don't get any.
Nicholas Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: I have.
Nicholas Roussos: Pull the dead, which is also something that I can use.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean…
Thomas Kolivakis: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, if you go to this directory, Go… if you go here, I created simpler web pages.
Kostadis Roussos: for looking at RPGBot, because I couldn't deal with his crap.
Nicholas Roussos: Whoa, whoa, whoa Sorry, they're not every day.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I have it for the Rogue. I didn't do it for the Monk. I'm sorry, I should do it for the Monk
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Nicholas Roussos: Sorry that not every computer scientist is a, Major. It's a major.
Nicholas Roussos: No, not every D and D player is a computer science major.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay, so let's see. What does he do? Calmer goes to ninth level.
Kostadis Roussos: That'd be great.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't get anything, I just get spells.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody's level 9?
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Kostadis Roussos: Actions, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Calmer needs to get a spell now, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, shit, let me do this.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys probably want Colmer to have good spells, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, boy.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, do we want to get commune so I can ask a god a question?
Kostadis Roussos: Greater restoration to restore us from any horrible.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, hold on, there' scrying so I could spy, or summon celestials so we could have one more ally.
Thomas Kolivakis: Mmm.
Thomas Kolivakis: I think Squine would be nice, but also… yeah.
Thomas Kolivakis: If you want to spy on, like, the other bosses.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Buying… you, scrying?
Thomas Kolivakis: But then I ask the gods could be also good.
Thomas Kolivakis: Since really, Temple of Elementoibo.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, scry, or greater restoration.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So I think you'll get greater restoration for the moment if we're if we're going to go because that some celestial data restoration, some celestial data restoration.
Kostadis Roussos: Summon Celestial. He's made up his mind.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm. Okay.
Thomas Kolivakis: What do you, what do you take?
Kostadis Roussos: It took greater restoration.
Thomas Kolivakis: No. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And just make sure to load it.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's have one more spell.
Kostadis Roussos: How many first level skills do I have?
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, what does, I recommend? The guy recommended for 4th level.
Kostadis Roussos: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Very good.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the word.
Kostadis Roussos: I already have that one.
Kostadis Roussos: 3rd level.
Kostadis Roussos: I didn't even know this call existed.
Kostadis Roussos: Astral flood.
Nicholas Roussos: What is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Come on.
Kostadis Roussos: Nothing, it's not a spell I.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: It's kind of like Fireball for clerics.
Nicholas Roussos: Burt's got a fireball.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh… Yeah, let me show you what it does.
Nicholas Roussos: That's interesting. What.
Kostadis Roussos: This is the news.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure.
Thomas Kolivakis: We're gonna use fireballs.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I just, just to give you an idea of what the spell does, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Why didn't I use this spell before?
Kostadis Roussos: Fulmer read about this spell. All right. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Take a long rest, everyone.
george: Oops.
Nicholas Roussos: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: And let's go to the first level, because that's where you're Layer is, yeah.
Thomas Kolivakis: Congrats.
Thomas Kolivakis: I mean, guys, now I can now mimic another person's speech or handwriting.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, nice.
Nicholas Roussos: Let's go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, yeah… Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I assume.
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
Kostadis Roussos: You know.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're sitting in your chambers, right? And then, Dren shows a knock on the door.
Nicholas Roussos: Morning, Ren, how'.
Thomas Kolivakis: Hello?
george: Early.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello.
Kostadis Roussos: Boss, there's a man outside, says Barkinar sent him to… Be the household.
Kostadis Roussos: Soft looking, gray, smiles too much.
Kostadis Roussos: I had Crail pat him down, he laughed about it, and let us… I don't trust him, but he does look…
Kostadis Roussos: harmless.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you let him in?
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, sure.
george: Good.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, forgive me, the intrusion.
Kostadis Roussos: And if it's okay, may I, I brought some wine. I'm…
Kostadis Roussos: Aldrin. Well, Lucius, Aldrin, when I'm working, it's a long story, and a dull one.
Kostadis Roussos: Barkinar, just to remind you, Barkinar is the guy who you met after you won the war, remember that?
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Well.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm… I'm working, it's a long story, and a dull one. Barkinar asked me to make sure the new management has everything it needs, and between us, I think he undersold the job.
Kostadis Roussos: Or profits in a day. The man could barely say it without smiling.
Kostadis Roussos: And he never smiles. Sit, sit! I brought you something to take the edge off, and then you're going to tell me what you're sort of, and I'm going to fix it. That's the whole of my talent. I carry things from clever people to clever people, and you four are the cleverest thing to happen here in a year!
Nicholas Roussos: What what will the last Clover's thing?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nicholas Roussos: Well, the last clever thing.
george: Happened a year ago.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, that's what I want to know.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll… That's a question for Barkinar.
Nicholas Roussos: Okay.
Thomas Kolivakis: Who's barking around again?
Nicholas Roussos: the guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Remember when you…
Kostadis Roussos: Remember when you guys defeated all the, all the forces of the, when you won the war?
Thomas Kolivakis: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: There was a guy who showed up and said, I had 4 problems in the morning and they're all gone.
Thomas Kolivakis: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the Barkinar.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh, he's, he.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he's the boss. He's the guy between you and the next layer of management.
Thomas Kolivakis: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: He also warned you about Senshot.
Nicholas Roussos: He's the next guy.
Kostadis Roussos: I warned you that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: He was also, Harsh's, he was the guy who was the head of the birth temple before Harsh got the, before he got promoted.
Thomas Kolivakis: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Kostadis Roussos: His relationship, so he's kind of an interesting character between you and whoever's above him. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, he says… but, as you…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, and I think that… I think he then says.
Kostadis Roussos: First of all, let me bring you this cask of excellent good wine. He clicks his fingers. Dren, could you bring that cask you told me to keep outside?
Kostadis Roussos: Boss, do you want me to bring the cask? I've heard of these casks exploding.
Thomas Kolivakis: Yeah.
Thomas Kolivakis: Bring it in.
Nicholas Roussos: Go ahead.
Kostadis Roussos: Dren turns to Zephyr and says, dude, I was talking to the boss. You and I are peers.
Kostadis Roussos: Palmer says…
Thomas Kolivakis: All right. Keep.
Kostadis Roussos: Calmer turns to Zephyr, turns to Dren and says, my dear Dren, I am more concerned with the spiritual matters of the earth.
Kostadis Roussos: the Earth Temple gods. I don't concern myself with these petty operational details. Please consult my… please talk to Sequoia, Zephyr, and Xenia for these things. Xenia will be in charge of all,
Thomas Kolivakis: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Intelligence Operations.
Thomas Kolivakis: Well, I'm clearly the most dominant guy here, so.
Thomas Kolivakis: I will…
Kostadis Roussos: Zephyr will be my chief operating officer for all things related to how we need to run the system, and Sequoia will be in charge of, well, making sure that things get into my hands and not out of my hands.
Nicholas Roussos: Yep. Got it.
Thomas Kolivakis: You've heard Kommer. Now, quick, get to my task. Task, whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so Kalmar sits down and starts reading, goes back to reading whatever he was reading. Okay, so you have a cask of genuinely good wine.
Kostadis Roussos: He also says, for the… Or the household.
Kostadis Roussos: And he provides you a potion of superior healing.
Nicholas Roussos: Are you trying to.
Thomas Kolivakis: I pour some, I pour some wine for, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Pour some wine for Lucius.
Thomas Kolivakis: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Then, he says, and here is a potion of superior healing.
Kostadis Roussos: Each.
Kostadis Roussos: Or the household.
Kostadis Roussos: So you all now have a potion of superior healing, so add that to your inventory.
Nicholas Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, guys, you're the heads of an evil temple, and he's your supply chain.
Thomas Kolivakis: That's true.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you do realize evil, right? I mean, you're the big bosses, right?
Nicholas Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: There is advantages to being the big bosses.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't forget to take a long rest, guys. Not that I'm expecting combat, but…
Thomas Kolivakis: 84%, okay.
Thomas Kolivakis: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty, and now… Just a couple things.
Thomas Kolivakis: Thank you, Luci.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I'm not done.
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh, my God.
Nicholas Roussos: Well, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: I forgot what.
Nicholas Roussos: The total amount of gold I was supposed to add from the.
Thomas Kolivakis: 583.
Kostadis Roussos: 745, 745.
Thomas Kolivakis: Sorry, man.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh wow, being being the head of an evil cult does have its benefits.
Thomas Kolivakis: I forgot, why is Lucian giving us all this?
Nicholas Roussos: Because we're the big… we're the… ahead.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you can ask… so you can ask him.
Thomas Kolivakis: Lucian, what do we owe all this loot?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, perhaps Bakunan didn't explain my role.
Thomas Kolivakis: No.
Kostadis Roussos: I see those. I my job is to make sure that what the temple needs, the temple gets. I'm sort of I meant.
Kostadis Roussos: I am the conduit from Nob to the temple, and one of my special privileges is to work with the leadership of the temple, and in this case that would be you, to get them whatever little thing they might need or want.
Thomas Kolivakis: Thank you. So might I ask if
Thomas Kolivakis: You could bring us to the to know, but so we could purchase some magical items.
Kostadis Roussos: But that's beneath you. I can procure these things, and let me make sure you know what I can procure.
Thomas Kolivakis: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Going to…
Nicholas Roussos: Oh yeah, we could get magic items without spending money right now.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you spend money, money still has to, money still has to be spent.
Nicholas Roussos: Damn.
Kostadis Roussos: But you don't have to go to Null, he acts as your middle.
Thomas Kolivakis: Tom, any, any dagger, magical dagger?
Thomas Kolivakis: I'd be most welcome.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me just,
Nicholas Roussos: Oh yeah, a magical dagger and a magical short sword would be really nice.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so let me just…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so,
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he says…
Kostadis Roussos: So, he says,
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he says, well, what is it that you need? Do you need something for survivability, mobility and infiltration?
Kostadis Roussos: Something to quickly run away, something to fight a caster, or some specific item that it will take me just a few days to collect.
Nicholas Roussos: Just, like… Bruce.
Kostadis Roussos: Because I knew that… hold on. Because I knew that you might need something… right now, on the…
Kostadis Roussos: On, on, right now, on lead time, let me just show you what I have. He,
Nicholas Roussos: You are completely right.
Kostadis Roussos: Jesus.
Kostadis Roussos: It randomly turns to Zephyr.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: How's my audio working now?
Nicholas Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, he turns… Dren turns to Zephyr. Boss.
Kostadis Roussos: Last time I checked, there's these chests that turn into mimics. Do you want me to bring the chest in?
Thomas Kolivakis: That's this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: If it turns into a mimic, I'm just outside. He brings the chest.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. He goes, well, let me see what we have here. I have a ring of protection.
Kostadis Roussos: For survivability. For mobility and infiltration, I have a hat of disguise.
Nicholas Roussos: Wait, did you say something in visibility?
Kostadis Roussos: No, ring of protection.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, sorry, I heard invisibility.
Kostadis Roussos: Infiltration.
Kostadis Roussos: Infiltration, not invisibility. To sneak inside.
Nicholas Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I have, sorry, I have several things. I have boots of levitation, a hat of disguise, or a ring of feather falling.
Nicholas Roussos: How much do they cost?
Kostadis Roussos: How much do they cost?
Nicholas Roussos: Do I have to buy them, or.
Kostadis Roussos: Unfortunately, yes, these are not free. I am a middleman and there are people I must pay. And Lord Hedrac has made it quite clear that although I'm offering these things, I'm not giving them away for free. The temple does have expenses that need to be paid.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, dumb.
Nicholas Roussos: Earth elementals cannot cost that much to maintain.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nicholas Roussos: Like, what's the maintenance cost on an elemental?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, all right, so I put the list there so you guys can see it.
Kostadis Roussos: of the things.
Nicholas Roussos: Anything, any, what?
Thomas Kolivakis: Let me see.
george: Regionally.
Thomas Kolivakis: Are we speaking to it?
Kostadis Roussos: Superior healing.
Kostadis Roussos: Just to be clear, the Potion of Superior Healing is what you already got, so that one was a free gift. That was a freebie.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh, a dagger of venom?
Kostadis Roussos: You already have… no, no, just instead of Dagger of Venom, just… if there's a one… there's a plus one… you want a plus one weapon of some kind.
Nicholas Roussos: I'll get the plus one weapon.
Thomas Kolivakis: You can take a shortcut plus one if you have.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, I'll also take a shortcut for.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so let me just tell you what the prices for that are.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you say? You said that you wanted a sword plus one, right?
Nicholas Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, that's a thousand gold pieces.
Nicholas Roussos: Deal.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Is there any, okay, Thomas, did you, did Zephyr also get one?
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, excellent choice, excellent choice. The blood, this was procured from… who was it procured from? Does it really matter? I hope you… I hope you use it to strike down the enemies of the temple and raise us all to greater power.
Nicholas Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Is there anything else you would like?
Kostadis Roussos: So, let me just say this, if you want to go do some research and come back to me next week, I'll assume that you did that, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: But it won't be given to you today, it'll show the DND list?
george: It's not good to annualize it.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know, let me just, I'm
Kostadis Roussos: If you go to D&D Beyond, right? Let me, I'm gonna send you a document. I'm gonna point, let me just do this. I'm gonna put a document.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm uploading a document, it'll take a few seconds there. You know.
Kostadis Roussos: So it's gonna take a few seconds to upload, and it's got… it's gonna be called Same Magical Prices, just go through there and pick something, okay?
george: Period.
george: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: These are the things he has right now. Everything else will take a few… 2 to 3 days.
Kostadis Roussos: If there's something that you want.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: Is there anything else that you guys see there that you might want?
Kostadis Roussos: By the way.
Kostadis Roussos: Things that are there might not be there in a day, in a day, so just keep that in mind.
Thomas Kolivakis: It's… Check.
Thomas Kolivakis: What is a dagger venom.
george: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You already have one of those.
Thomas Kolivakis: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: That's the…
george: What kind of monkey?
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, the issue with the monkey, there's not anything useful. You don't get any.
Nicholas Roussos: Armor.
Nicholas Roussos: I mean, I guess there's some rings that you could get.
george: The rings.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so for example, for you, things that would help are Boots of Levitation, because it helps.
Thomas Kolivakis: I'll take that.
Kostadis Roussos: Different direction.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, let him… you can get lots of things, he's a little bit more restrained. Rings of protection are also good, because they give you better armor class.
george: How much should they both cost? Okay, fine.
george: I'm…
Kostadis Roussos: It doesn't catch.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: 3,500 gold pieces.
george: Which one?
Kostadis Roussos: But a ring of protection, a ring of protection.
george: Okay, let's see what it.
Kostadis Roussos: It's actually a very useful item.
george: Boost.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you find.
george: Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I think it also gives you… it also gives you other abilities, I think.
george: Add saving throughs, plus one to saving throughs.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that is a big deal.
george: Okay, I'll get one for 3,000.
Nicholas Roussos: Wait, what? That's a little powerful.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Nicholas Roussos: What was it called? The ring…
Kostadis Roussos: Uhm… Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Bring your protection plus one.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I thought…
Nicholas Roussos: I didn't want to realize I added one key saving to us.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, that's why it Let's give it to the monk who can't wear armor, doesn't wear weap.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah, the monk should get it. I was just mentioning that seemed very powerful.
Kostadis Roussos: So it is very powerful. That's why it's 3,500 gold pieces.
Nicholas Roussos: Jesus.
Kostadis Roussos: Oops.
george: Oh, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you are.
Kostadis Roussos: You are correct, it is very powerful.
Nicholas Roussos: Mason, man, you're about to go in debt, d.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll have to think about what Calmer wants,
Kostadis Roussos: Off the top of my head, I can't think of something
Kostadis Roussos: Zephyr, is there anything that you want from that list, or do you want to think about it for a week? Think about it.
Thomas Kolivakis: Good for now. That's it. Oh, it says hi.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Thomas Kolivakis: Says pipe.
Kostadis Roussos: Where do you see pipe?
Thomas Kolivakis: Oh, we're in the wrong thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Boots of levitation, hat of disguise, ring of feather falling Ocean of Speed.
Kostadis Roussos: Bell scrolls teleport.
Kostadis Roussos: It's the staff that's drink.
Thomas Kolivakis: feather falling, is that the, like… jump from anyone.
Kostadis Roussos: Basically, you can't fall down and get hurt.
Thomas Kolivakis: I'll wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Go away.
Kostadis Roussos: It'll,
Kostadis Roussos: Some kind of staff was striking, or something that we already had, so… I think it's
Kostadis Roussos: Striking.
Kostadis Roussos: That one is 21,000 gold pieces. He cannot afford it.
Nicholas Roussos: What if?
Kostadis Roussos: The Staff of Striking is 21,000 gold pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: A very rare magical item.
Kostadis Roussos: What does it do? It acts as a…
Kostadis Roussos: Plus 3 bonus to attack rolls and damage rolls. It has 10 charges. When you hit with a melee attack using it, you can expend up to 3 charges. For each charge you expend, the target takes an extra 1d6 force damage.
Thomas Kolivakis: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
george: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, oh, hold on. I missed one. Sorry, Nick.
Nicholas Roussos: Yup.
Kostadis Roussos: Two.
Kostadis Roussos: There's these… these might be of interest to somebody.
Nicholas Roussos: I'll take the.
Kostadis Roussos: We have invisibility.
Kostadis Roussos: A ring of invisibility or a ring of reaction?
Nicholas Roussos: How much is the Ring of Invisibility.
Kostadis Roussos: That one's very expensive, 10,000 gold pieces.
Nicholas Roussos: Oh yeah, that's not happening.
Thomas Kolivakis: What's the ringer reaction?
Kostadis Roussos: That is also very expensive, 20,000 gold pieces.
Nicholas Roussos: Why is that so good?
Kostadis Roussos: Free action can't be a paralyzed, held, Like…
Kostadis Roussos: All difficult terrain appears as normal terrain. It basically means that any monster that has the ability to affect the terrain or to slow you down can't affect you.
Nicholas Roussos: Why did that happen with a free action?
Kostadis Roussos: called ring of reaction.
Nicholas Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: That's why it's called. It means that you are never the ring of reactionism.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, while you're wearing this ring, difficult terrain doesn't cost you extra movement. In addition, magic can neither reduce any of your speeds nor cause you to have paralyzed or restrained conditions.
Thomas Kolivakis: Well, when I get the money, I'll get.
Nicholas Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Just so you know what it is.
Kostadis Roussos: Palmer, Lucia says.
Kostadis Roussos: I… Zephyr, as much as I would like to promise that this would always be here, I think that if you wish to keep it on the back, so that I wouldn't sell it, a small deposit of 4,000 gold pieces would be necessary.
Kostadis Roussos: I do have other buyers.
Thomas Kolivakis: 4,000 gold pieces?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Thomas Kolivakis: And it's how much in total.
Kostadis Roussos: Ring of reaction?
Kostadis Roussos: There's 20,000.
Thomas Kolivakis: No, we will not be playing this.
Kostadis Roussos: And for you, Nicholas, the ring of invisibility, he offers to keep it.
Kostadis Roussos: Away from people for, 4,000 gold pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: So when you have the rest of the money, you can buy it. That way, it doesn't go away.
Kostadis Roussos: Of course, you may end up killing him or whatever, but I'm just telling you, like, that's where the situation is.
Nicholas Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nicholas Roussos: Well.
Kostadis Roussos: You good?
Nicholas Roussos: Yep.
Nicholas Roussos: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, being the evil bosses has its advantages, yes?
george: Yep.
Nicholas Roussos: Yep.
Thomas Kolivakis: It's a little poor You must do it.
Kostadis Roussos: There's…
Nicholas Roussos: Alright, see y.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, there's more money to be… all of a sudden, you become motivated to get more money, right?
Nicholas Roussos: Yep. All right. See you guys.
george: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.